Hi everyone, I'm Kirill Danyukov, a 2nd-year student at the Center-College of Applied Qualifications.
皆さん、こんにちは。キリル・ダニュコフと申します。応用資格センター・カレッジの2年生です。
I am running for the position of head of the cultural and events committee.
私は文化・大衆活動委員会の委員長に立候補しています。
Since my school days, I have often participated in various events.
学生時代からずっと、さまざまなイベントに積極的に参加してきました。
At one point, I attended the Center for the Development of Modern Competencies for Children, where I learned video editing and filming,
かつて子ども現代スキル開発センターに通い、動画の編集・撮影を学びました。
as well as how to properly present myself in front of an audience.
また、人前での正しいふる舞い方も学びました。
After I enrolled at the Center-College of Applied Qualifications,
応用資格センター・カレッジに入学してからは、
I started engaging in creative activities, mainly KVN (a comedy team competition show).
創作活動、主にКВН（ロシアのコメディ番組КВН）に取り組み始めました。
At the moment I have my own KVN team, of which I am the leader.
現在は自分のКВНチームを持っており、私がそのリーダーを務めています。
If I become head of the cultural and events committee, I will add the following to my work program.
もし私が文化・大衆活動委員会の委員長になれたなら、以下のことを活動計画に加えます。
The first thing I will add is quizzes related to culture, literature, and theater.
まず第一に、文化・文学・演劇に関連したクイズを追加します。
The second thing I will add is quests related to one era or another.
第二に、特定の時代にちなんだクエストを追加します。
For example, about the culture of the 2000s or the 1990s.
たとえば、2000年代や90年代の文化をテーマにしたものです。
And third, something you will find very interesting — KVN and stand-up comedy.
そして第三に、皆さんにきっと楽しんでもらえるКВНとスタンダップをやります。
And the most important question: why should you choose me as head of the cultural and events committee?
さて、最も重要な質問です。なぜ私を文化・大衆活動委員会の委員長に選ぶべきなのでしょうか？
First of all, I want to organize events that bring people closer together.
まず第一に、人と人とをつなぐイベントを作りたいと思っています。
I want to create not just events from the student council, but events that several organizations will work on together.
学生評議会だけのイベントではなく、複数の組織が協力して取り組むイベントを作りたいのです。
For example, the Michurinsky Volunteer Corps (MVC), Monolit, and Dvizheniye Pervykh (Movement of the First).
たとえば、ミチュリンスク・ボランティア・コープス（МВК）、モノリット、そして「最初の動き」（Движение первых）です。
And finally, what I want to say is: protection and support are my duty to the people who voted for me.
最後に言いたいことは、私に投票してくれた人たちを守り、支えることが私の義務だということです。